[Music]
[Música]
javi with this image we will miss you we love you
javi con esta imagen te extrañaremos te
fired from me firing him from my good
despedido de mi despedirlo de mi buena
family are the hazards of the trade it happens to me like a
familia son gajes del oficio me pasa por
fool it happens to me like a
tonto me pasa por tonto
fool it happens to me like a fool it happens to me like a fool
me pasa por tonto
oh javier if I can't see well be
ay javier si es que no vea bien sea
good the move is the next one okay the
bueno la movida es la siguiente vale la
move is that yesterday dallas
movida es que ayer dallas
suddenly put up
de repente puso
the following tweet god I just
puso el siguiente tuit dios me acabo de
found out something really strong a super
enterar de una cosa fuertísima un
famous streamer is a piece of
streamer famosísimo es un pedazo de
abuser and on top of that his fans justify him and
abusador y encima su fan lo justifican y
lick his balls I'm really
le lamen los huevos yo de verdad estoy
hallucinating and I'm even more hallucinating that
alucinando y alucino aún más que la
people have been trying to hide what
gente ha estado tratando de ocultar lo
their friends knew soon video
que sus amigos lo sabían pronto vídeo
okay well people started
vale bien la gente empezó a hacer
speculating about this tweet not
especulaciones sobre este tuit no
saying that it could be spring they
diciendo que podría ser spring a mí me
told me it could be sprint because of the
dijeron que podría ser sprint por el
tweet they exchanged that giving them he put
tweet que se cruzaron que darles le puso
something like that without consent I don't know what
algo así de sin consentimiento no sé qué
what he told you joye it's a joke I don't know
que os dijo joye será una broma no sé
what and well well it's not it's not spring what
qué y bueno pues no lo es no es spring
else did they tell me you told me several
que más me dijeron me dijisteis varias
options you didn't give me several options
opciones no me disteis varias opciones
but  well people
pero bueno la gente
none of them got it right, honestly I didn't
ninguno acertó yo sinceramente no
know this story about Coco I don't know if
conocía esta historia de coco no sé si
you guys would know it but I've
ustedes la conocería y pero me he
been freaking out hallucinating and
quedado flipando alucinando y realmente
I really think that I'm honest
yo creo que sé sincero
I'm starting out with a mess in white hands
me estreno con lío en blanco manos
clapping hands clapping hands clapping
aplaudiendo manos aplaudiendo manos
but we love you so
aplaudiendo pero te queremos muchísimo
much thank you so much for that super chat and
muchísimas gracias por ese super chat y
now you have white lion we've known each other for
ya tienes león blanco ya nos conocemos
so long incredible incredible you have to
desde hace tanto tiempo
keep
increíble increíble me tienes que quedar
this filter for life to look
con este filtro de por vida para parecer
young that I don't know if you knew I
joven que yo no sé si lo sabíais he
saw del sur talk about the subject at the time
visto del sur hablar del tema en su día
almost two years ago but I don't know if he
hace casi dos años pero yo no sé si lo
knew and yes I want to comment on a couple of
sabía y sí que quiero comentar un par de
things okay before seeing all the material
cosas vale antes de ver todo el material
point number one there is a part of the video
punto número uno hay una parte del vídeo
that some of you have sent like
que algunos habéis mandado como que
Dallas says that he has known for a
dallas dice que lo sabe desde hace un
year or that we knew for a year but
año o que lo supimos de hace un año pero
then it is contradictory with what he says
luego es contradictorio con lo que dice
in the tweet in which he says that yes he just found
en el tweet en el que dice que sí que se
out no of course here there were
acaba de enterar no claro aquí había
several options that Dallas actually did
varias opciones que dallas en realidad
know for a long time and
si lo supiera desde hace mucho tiempo y
suddenly he released the video because of the
de repente haya sacado el vídeo por la
controversy in the tweets  of the last few
polémica de los tweets de las últimas
hours
horas
that could be a legitimate thing and that is
que podría ser una cosa lícita y que se
done
hace
is the action of human beings on many
es el actuar del ser humano en muchas
occasions 1
ocasiones 1 punto número 2 qué es lo que
point number 2 what I have verified and it does not refer to that it refers to the fact that the bomb exploded a year and a half ago or almost 2 no but that he has found out now as he says in the tweet okay in fact on several occasions during the video
en varias ocasiones durante el vídeo
repeat it and I verified that some magicians
repítelo y comprobaba que algunos magos
send messages and not look at the team
mandan mensajes y no mirada al equipo
shout I knew I knew and he has kept quiet about it
gritar sabía lo sabía y se lo ha callado
until now that about the tweet no no I did not
hasta ahora que lo del tweet no no no lo
know I did not know I for example did not
sabía no lo sabía yo por ejemplo no lo
know I do not know I do not know
sabía no sé si ustedes lo sabíais voy a
here a couple of things that he sends me
ver aquí un par de cositas que me manda
so that I can check it I hope not to eat
para que lo compruebe espero no comerme
anything strange again
nada raro de nuevo
in
en
the adversity of that that does that but
la adversidad de esa que hace esa pero
please
por favor
well tense it is compensating me a little for
bueno tensa me está compensando un poco
the two or three days that I will not be no thank you
los dos o tres días que no estaré no
heaven thank you very much to Kevin
gracias cielo muchísimas gracias a kevin
thank you very much
muchas gracias
and well that I saw thank you very much well I have to I have to
y bueno que vi muchas gracias bueno
loosen that that
tengo que tengo que aflojar esa
alert that thanks to the heart
esa alerta que gracias al corazón
thank you very much
gracias muchas gracias
yes
sí
[Music]
[Música]
this thing about the green hearts is
esto de los corazones verdes es
making progress okay because
haciéndose el progreso vale porque a de
suddenly it is done as although it is very
repente se hace como aunque es muy
progressive point number 2 the other thing I
progres a punto número 2 lo otro que
wanted to comment that I do not understand how he was going to go
quería comentar que yo no entiendo como
if he knows this he does not know but well if he is a
si sabe esto no lo sabe pero bueno si es
friend you do not know when jail a they are
colega no sabes cuándo cárcel a son
colleagues I do not understand that he was going to go
colegas yo no entiendo que iba a ir
invite these people to the events or
invite a esta gente a los eventos o sea
literally look at the other friend monkey I
literalmente mira el otro el amigo mono
have nothing against them
no tengo nada en contra de ellos
what there is is that they have acted horribly in front of
lo que hay es que han actuado fatal de
the public
cara al público
as if he is the friend we were talking
como que es el amigo estuvimos hablando
about him on this channel because he
de él en este canal porque
threatened win to win michu he made a
amenazó a win to win michu hizo un
joke in bad taste and you may like
chiste de mal gusto y os puede caer
win michu more or less in fact we
mejor o peor win michu de hecho
probably do not like win michu very much
seguramente no nos caiga muy bien win
for certain things not without reasons
michu por ciertas cosas no sin motivos
that we have criticized many times
que hemos criticado muchísimas veces
but we do not have to threaten anyone with
pero no hay que amenazar a nadie con
violence okay and momo threatened win
violencia vale y momo amenazó a win
michu it is like man we are not in the jungle
michu es como tío no estamos en la selva
nor are we in the ghetto he has or I mean this
ni estamos en el ghetto tiene o sea esto
is a society okay the differences are
es una sociedad vale las diferencias se
debated and criticized okay but those
debaten y se critican vale pero esas no
are not the ways okay they
son las formas vale
are people that the truth is I do not see them very
son gente que la verdad no las veo muy
civilized in the current way and now
civilizada a la forma actual y que ahora
you put  since you're in fashion and you're
te pongas como estás de moda y están
living like now you're famous and
viviendo en plan ahora ya eres famoso y
now the brands collaborate with you
ahora ya las marcas colaboran contigo
now green hearts
ahora corazones verdes
[Music] being
[Música]
able to rape perfect women
pudiendo violarse a mujeres perfectas
as such and they raped Zulma Lobato if
como tal y se violaron a zulma lobato si
you're going to go to jail for your whole life do the
vas a ir preso a toda tu vida hace la
right thing
bien
how they like whoring in
como les gusta el [__] en gente
older people grew up in the environment leave
grande crecía en el ambiente dejen en
Bruno alone that the boy was going to meet a
paz a bruno que el chico iba a conocer
thousand people worthwhile while
mil personas que valgan la pena mientras
those who were only looking for a minute
pasan esas que sólo buscaban un minuto
of fame pass by I
de fama
didn't want to tweet [ __ ] about that
no quería twittear una [__] de ese
subject but when I see older people throwing fuel on the fire
tema pero cuando veo tirar leña al fuego
I get outraged
a gente grande me indignó
the staff is being a fake
el personal está siendo un careta
people
la gente
[Music]
[Música]
Frank is an atomic turn he's already I don't
frank es un viraje atómico ya tiene no
know how many years old and he still seems like a
sé cuántos años y sigue pareciendo un
kid as always sticking his nose in where he shouldn't
nene como siempre metiéndose donde no
and delaying everything I end up
debe y atrasando todo acabe
understanding
entendiendo
oh well what's causing controversy okay shitty face
ah bueno que hace polémicas vale
come on play the
careta de [__] dale hacete de la
victim
víctima
[Music]
[Música]
yes
sí
it's not going to make you seek
que no te va a llevar a buscar la
conscience
conciencia
if I
si
don't understand this video I don't understand the
no entiendo este vídeo no entiendo el
video  this was supposed to be exposing
vídeo este se supone que era exponiendo
things about coco but well let's see taking
cosas de coco pero bueno a ver echando
a look at the most important parts
un vistazo a las partes más importantes
of what dallas has exposed okay
de lo que ha expuesto dallas vale
the confession and the ridiculous excuse well
la confesión y la excusa ridícula bien
this is the issue can't imagine loving yourself an
esto es el tema no imagina quererte un
influencer as a 13 14 15 year old and
influences de nene de 13 14 15 años y
doing these things instead of teaching
hacer estas cosas en vez de enseñarle a
kids that women should be
los nenes que a las mujeres hay que
respected I would be ashamed to be your
respetarla me daría vergüenza ser tu
mother and see this then say being with a
madre y ver esto después decir estar con
girl with a green heart little man
piba con el corazón verde poco hombre
cocu violin okay
cocu violín vale
this is the click that says age let's
este es el click que pone edad la vamos
listen to it because I don't really understand
a escucharlo porque no entiendo muy bien
the move d
la movida d
justified the excuse to [ __ ] with me
justificado la excusa para [__] conmigo
[ __ ] drunk
[__] borracha
if he called an ambulance friend
si llamó a una ambulancia amigo
from college or rather a girl who
de la facultad o sea una chica que
was with him suddenly got very
estaba con él de repente se puso muy
drunk he doesn't drink and she got very
borracha él no bebe y ella se puso muy
drunk and he didn't know what to do and what he
borracha y él no sabía qué hacer y lo
came up with was to open open stream
que se le ocurrió fue abrir abrir stream
these factors also that
estos factores también
happened from streaming meaning he went to
eso pasó de streaming o sea que se fue a
ask his followers for advice on stream he
pedir consejo a sus seguidores en stream
pressed 8 in the morning and the remote control
pulsaba las 8 de la mañana y el mando
of the house passed to me  I didn't know what to
de la casa me pasó a mí yo no sabía qué
do and
hacer y
learn to write complete llanera
aprender a escribir completa llanera
so as not to show the girl turned on the
para no mostrar a la niña prendió el
string with the black screen the photo of
string con la pantalla negra la foto de
the mine already sent it to all his
la mina ya se la mandó a todos sus
colleagues
colegas
to the people what do I do what do I do I
a la gente qué hago qué hago
was in the fifth dream in the sixth
estaba en el quinto sueño en el sexto
and of course she was asleep I was in the
y claro estaba dormida estaba en el
fifth dream naked and I took a picture
quinto sueño desnuda y me hice una foto
with her but how
con ella pero como
are you telling that like it was so
estás contando eso así como si fuera tan
normal
normal
already who the [ __ ] are you telling me
ya quién [__] estás contándome
what the [ __ ] and well we even had sex until
qué [__] y bueno echamos hasta que
there was a violin which was a hashtag that there was
hubo con violín que fue un hashtag que
no
hubo no
that photo was passed to momo when the
esa foto se la pasó a momo cuando la
girl fell asleep ha ha ha ha ha he told it
mina se durmió ja ja ja ja ja lo contó
in an anecdote
en una anécdota
viola with q viola
viola con q viola
who sent him those photos careful and it's
que le mandó esas fotos cuidados y
also true
también es verdad
da not only did he take a look
da no sólo echó un vistazo
that he told that photo
que esa foto
as an anecdote that
la contó como anécdota
he told that photo as an anecdote man well like a culture I was really drunk and I took a picture dude and this happened and it went viral in 2020 and they invite them to events and even as protagonists I don't understand the issue of the youtubers of the stream in  many times
youtubers de los stream en muchas veces
I don't understand many times that when
yo no entiendo muchas veces que cuando
someone falls into grace and is
alguien como que cae en gracia y forma
part of a certain little group they already come to the
parte del cierto grupito ya viene a los
salsa channels super caca on the
canales de salsa super caca en los
sanse channels or super kak we don't
canales del sanse o super kaká no los
want them here that can't make a
queremos aquí que no puede hacer un
video at night when I'm not
vídeo por la noche cuando no estoy
playing gta
jugando al gta
this one is invited by a person who was born in
ya este lo invitan persona que nació en
bolivia in a greengrocer hello sir what do you
bolivia en una verdulería hola señor que
need in return will a chinese
necesita en cambio te atiende un chino
oriental japanese or from that
oriental japonés o de esa cultura
oriental culture serve you rude daughter of a [ __ ] will
oriental maleducada hija de [__] te
serve you in a Haitian supermarket that
atiende en un supermercado haitiana que
are made of 50 pesos not chinese
están hechas de 50 pesos no chinos
idiots tell me it's 50 pesos how much are you going to
[__] decime son 50 pesos con cuánto
pay speak to me nice chinese imbecile I'm
vas a pagar háblame bien chino imbécil
not speaking to you nicely and yes I already
no te estoy hablando bien y si ya te
told you currently your local quote is
digo la actualmente tu local citó de
shitty because you have cockroaches that
[__] porque tienes cucarachas que
walk on the walls when I
caminan por las paredes cuando yo te
greet you and say I come to buy it now
saludo y te digo la vengo a comprar ya
your local shitty that is full of
tu local de [__] que está lleno de
filth say hello to me who the [ __ ] taught you
mugre salúdame quién [__] te enseño
with if you are in my country in Argentina that
con si estás en mi país en argentina que
in my country and I can have to adapt to
en mi país y puedo tener que adecuar a
the rules of my country chinese idiot
las reglas de mi país chino [__] la
your mother's [ __ ] no no I don't hate them I
concha de tu madre no no los odio los
hate them and the Chinese are real I hate them
odios y los chinos son reales los odio
if I endured you hard the Bolivians
si os duramente aguante los bolivianos
the Paraguayans and you discriminate against the
los paraguayos y usted discrimina de los
Bolivians and the Paraguayans do not
bolivianos y de los paraguayos no
discriminate
discriminan
but man ibai that ibai that many nights
pero tío ibai que ibai que muchas noches
are here watching some video before
están aquí viendo algún vídeo antes de
going to bed or even in the
irte a la cama o incluso en el propio
live itself you often see
directo en vivo estás muchas veces
what the selection is because there are people that there are
cuál es la selección porque hay gente a
people that don't
la que hay gente a la que no
because I don't understand the truth I
porque es que no entiendo la verdad o
mean I can't understand
sea no puedo entender
well don't go buy a place if
pues no vayas a comprar un sitio si no
you don't like the place because there are cockroaches
te gusta el sitio porque hay cucarachas
or I mean sale buy a cleaner place
o sea que venta compra un sitio más
wow let's see from here if it
limpio guau a ver a partir de aquí si
can go up more or less
puede subir más o menos
because you already put efe
porque ya ponéis efe
more banned
más baneado
handled the tweet
manejado el tuit
and I fell I
y me caí
fell oman banned I have
me caí omán baneado
returned
he regresado
brown they are going to handle me today surely
brown me van a manejar hoy seguramente
that has failed of course he told him with
que haya fracasado claro le dijo con
plays the other day or audio
jugadas el otro día o audio
I am understanding because there are more and
estoy entendiendo porque hay cada vez
more gays the women are all really crazy
más gays las mujeres están todas re loca
earnings of February 2014 not to
haberes de febrero 2014 no es por
justify it but some nonsense
justificar lo pero alguna burrada
see if you put me  maybe a tweet like
a ver si me pones a lo mejor un tuit en
your disgusting son I think that almost
plan tu hij asqueroso yo creo que casi
all of us have some people even
todos tenemos alguna gente incluso a la
that we like today and in which we
que nos cae bien hoy y en la que
want I'm sure if I had the twitter
queremos yo seguro si tuviera el twitter
archive for ten years and they weren't tweets from the new one I'm
archivo y no fueron tweets del nuevo
sure I could have scratched some
seguro que se me podía rascar algún
sexist or racist tweet or some thing you
tweet machista o racista o alguna cosa
know that it's a specific tweet a
seguro sabe que sea un tweet puntual un
specific event okay but it seems to me that
hecho puntual vale pero me parecen que
these are too many things
estos son demasiadas cosas
beyond that you don't like him give the
más allá de que no te caiga bien da la
review it doesn't justify the crime
review no da para justificar el delito
that the piece of coconut abuser committed
que cometió el pedazo de abusador de
anyway the selective feminist
coco en fin la feminista selectiva
defends a lost cause
defiende en un caso perdido
imagine being a feminist and supporting something
imagínate ser feminista y apoyar algo
that is clear that now many people
que sea claro que ahora mucha gente
[Music]
[Música]
something good and soda la of course there will be
algo bueno y soda la claro es que habrá
many people like that like they hate
mucha gente como que como que odien al
Dallas no and since they hate Dallas then they
dallas no y como odian al dallas pues
defend Coco no surely the
defienden al coco no seguramente la
movement will be that way no let's
movida será por ahí no
see let's see here more or less
a ver vamos a ver por aquí más o menos
because here we've already seen it he's famous they
porque aquí ya lo hemos visto es famoso
want to smoke it we're talking about that
lo quieren fumar lo estamos hablando de
guy saying something politically
que el tipo dijera algo políticamente
incorrect that he's also a piece of
incorrecto que también es un pedazo de
racist that you [ __ ] for  you will see clips
racista que te cagas para veréis clips
of that but we are talking about
de eso sino que estamos hablando de que
this guy being an abuser and his friend
el tipejo este es un abusador y su amigo
momo being an accomplice in his right mind with
el momo es un cómplice en [__] en su
an
punto sano juicio de una persona
unconscious person at home drugged up the only thing
inconsciente en casa drogada lo único
you can think of is to take a [ __ ]
que se te ocurre es sacarte una [__]
selfie and with it you piece of sick [ __ ] these
self y con ella pedazo de enfermo estos
fans of his really no
sus fans de [__] de verdad ningún
repulsive fandom to defend him and
fandom repulsivo que le defiendan y
on top of that do not extend this news
encima no extiendan esta noticia más
beyond this because
allá de esto porque esto no se enteró
practically nobody found out about this either you guys do
prácticamente nadie también ya vosotros
n't have the slightest idea that
no tenéis ni la más remota idea de que
this became famous and look at the gold I
esto se hizo famoso y fijaos el oro me
found out and I am a salt channel that
enteré y soy un canal de sal se o que se
finds out about everything more or less and I did not
entera de todo más o menos y yo no me
find out
entere
comments want to take it down because there is
comentarios lo quieren bajar porque es q
no more you are hitting me and there is no
no hay más me estás pegando y no hay
hair and it is under the 190 likes rule
mato pelo y está bajo la regla 190 likes
what bhutto disgusting I swear this is
que bhutto ascos lo juro esto es
vomitous it is vomitous that people
vomitivo es vomitivo que la gente
can justify an act like this that is
alcance justificar un acto así que es
literally an abuse look at this
literalmente un abuso fijaos en esta
chick because on top of that it is women who
tipa porque encima son mujeres las que
defend her the concept of canceling
le defienden el concepto de cancelar
celebrities for very old tweets it is
famosos por tweets viejísimos es una
[ __ ]  because all of us as kids had
[__] porque todos de [__] tuvimos
stupid things and we don't have a bit of
boludeces y no tenemos ni un poco de
conscience, I know how each one
conciencia yo haya cada uno como fue
changed in life, nobody knows if he still
cambiando en la vida nadie sabe si sigue
thinks the same as in the tweets, only
pensando igual que en los tweets solo
people close to u2, fer mancha version,
gente cercana de u2 versión fer mancha
nobody so in his adolescence and it
nadie así que en su adolescencia y le
happens to him that if you have a drugged
ocurre que si tienes una persona drogada
and unconscious person in your house, the best thing
e inconsciente en tu casa lo mejor que
you can think of is to take a [ __ ] selfie
se te ocurre es hacerte una puñetera
and with it and send your
self y con ella y mandar a tus puntos
friends to see how a girl
colegas para que vean cómo una chica
is unconscious and naked, the logical thing
está inconsciente y desnudando lo lógico
that crossed your mind about another, no, there
que se te pasó por la cabeza de otra no
is no way to turn that
no hay manera de darle la vuelta a ese
matter around in homes it is abuse this point is disgusting,
asunto en casas es abuso este punto asco
see, he assured, equipped with a rage, you are going to
ver aseguró equipado de un cabreo vais a
change, it is more kindly at price more
cambiar es más amablemente a price más
than those of the west of the cause, take care of it a
que las que los oeste del cause cuide al
month, he is obsessed with
mes está obsesionado con las mujeres
sexy women, that he is a true misogynist and a
sexy que es un verdadero misógino y un
misogynist with all the letters in a
misógino con todas las letras en un
lot of tweets saying that all
montón de tweet diciendo que todas las
women are really crazy, that on women's day,
mujeres están re locas que el día de la
this disgusting one says happy with
mujer el asqueroso este dice feliz con
hysterical doubts, beautiful and so
dudas histéricas hermosas y tan
necessary women feel look at this
necesarias mujeres se sienten mira esto
from the tries what I tell you, be yes,
de los tries lo que te digo sea sí que
we have seen some youtube  that in
hemos visto algún youtube que en
2013-2014
2013-2014
even not so far back he had tweets that
incluso no tan lejos tenía tweets que
are truly absurd that cross
son verdaderas burradas que traspasan
any limit no but they were other
cualquier límite no pero eran otros
times and a half that if it were only
tiempos y medio que si solamente fuera
that you know how I have done isolated' well
eso sabes como he hecho aislado' bueno
to him if it were only fact done as I have
a él si solamente fuera hecho hecho como
done isolated well but the
he hecho aislado bueno pero es que el
set that we have family is the
conjunto que tenemos familia es el
set that we have of things having
conjunto que tenemos de cosas teniendo
because there are more and more gays women
porque cada vez hay más gays las mujeres
are all crazy if women
están todas locas si las mujeres no
weren't hysterical there would be
fuesen histéricas existiría la paz
world peace dying raping
mundial muriendo violarse a mujeres
perfect women like cloud and they raped
perfectas como cloud y se violaron a
zulma lobato or be me does go to jail
zulma lobato o seas yo hace ir preso
your whole life he is very jealous of a lot of scum of
toda tu vida cela bien en mucha escoria
his shitty fans justifying that
de sus fans de [__] justificando que
these tweets are from 2014 you have to be
estos tweets son de 2014 hay que estar
sick it's that the fact that they are only tweets
enfermo es que los que sólo sean tweets
is that he balances his lie he dedicated himself to
es que equilibra miente dedicaba a
spreading photos without consent of
difundir fotos sin consentimiento de
unconscious alcoholic drugged girls in his [ __ ] house that he
inconscientes en su [__] casa que la
sent to his shitty friends who are the
mandaba a sus colegas de [__] que son
same as him and he is in charge of spreading
iguales que él y se encarga de difundir
this [ __ ] [ __ ]
esta [__] [__] de material de
content material that if it were really less the
contenido que de ser realmente menos la
girl is for me and nobody has done  these
chica es por mí y nadie ha hecho estas
things not even when I was a teenager if you did it it
cosas ni cuando era adolescente si tú lo
's because he's a piece of
has hecho es porque es un pedazo de
[ __ ] because on top of that this guy
enfermo es que encima este tipejo de
here was 25 years old when this
aquí tenía 25 años cuando esto había
happened he was not a teenager
ocurrido no era ningún adolescente
javi I'm sure we saw that clip on
javi estoy segura que vimos ese clip en
this witness channel from 2019 but what we
este canal testigo del 2019 pero lo que
saw was the I don't drink alcohol thing it doesn't
vimos fue lo del yo no bebo alcohol no
sound familiar to me that we saw it
me suena a mí eso que lo viéramos
but Veracruz I am a senile grandfather
pero veracruz yo soy un abuelo senil lo
we saw the same thing and I don't remember pp even if
mismo lo vimos y no me acuerdo pp aunque
it was that does not justify absolutely
lo fuese eso no justifica absolutamente
anything that someone says there is no context
nada que alguien dice no existe contexto
or situation for the girl was a minor that
o situación para chica era menor que
justifies taking a photo or an
justifica el sacar una foto o una mina
unconscious girl is naked and sending it
inconsciente está en pelotas y mandarse
to a friend it simply does not exist and says
a un amigo simplemente no existe y dice
a shitty fan of this exists look an
un fan de [__] de este existe mira un
extra touch the biggest one above is the
toque extra la mayor arriba está el
video you can upload with the
vídeo puedes subir con la rueda del
mouse wheel or the other there
mouse o del otro
is a part of the video that came out like
hay una parte del vídeo que salía como
a news story on the news here is the
una noticia en telediario aquí está la
[ __ ] rabble this guy also
[__] gentuza este tipejo además se
dedicates himself to bragging about a lot of
dedica a vanagloriar un montón de
ultra progress games as if he was
partidos ultra progress como si el fue
an ally of the host as typical I
un aliado de la [__] como típico los
told them the news said that also to
dije las noticias decían que además a
a girl under what happened this
una chica menor de lo que sucedió este
exact  he is a streamer basically a
exacto es un streamer básicamente una
civilian martin perez is somewhat better known
civil martín pérez es algo más conocido
as 'el cuco' square mix and is well
como 'el cuco' square mix y es muy
known for dedicating himself precisely to this
conocido por dedicarse justamente a esto
to broadcast live gaming sessions
a transmitir en vivo sesiones de juego
there what we are seeing is an image
ahí lo que estamos viendo es una imagen
in which he is seen several years ago
en la que se lo ve a él hace varios años
with a naked girl an
junto con una chica desnuda una menor de
underage is also moving some tweets
edad también está moviendo unos tweets
for example from the year 2014 gratitude
por ejemplo del año 2014 gratitud
idolaters at the cost finish you look at it
idólatras al costo terminar te lo mirar
to see who the [ __ ] you are supporting to
a ver a quién [__] estás apoyando a
see who the [ __ ] you are making famous a
ver a quién [__] estás haciendo famoso
guy who is dedicated to abusing
a un tipo que se dedica a abusar de
women and goes around insulting
mujeres y va insultando
if you are watching a
si estáis viendo de
chronicle that it is not a reliable medium
crónica de que no es un medio fiable
to see family that does not matter
para ver familia que no da igual
okay but the Christian fact
vale pero el hecho cristiano
the fact does exist we do not take it down because
el hecho si existe no lo bajamos porque
because it appears in that shitty medium
porque sale en ese medio de [__]
the fact if it is healthy
el hecho si es sano
the fact if he did it
el hecho si lo hizo no
we have not seen the video of him laughing with
hemos visto el vídeo de él riéndose con
a friend look what occurred to me I opened
un amigo mira lo que se me ocurrió abrí
string I took the photo
string me hice la foto
the reality in which no although it
la realidad en la que no aunque haya
appeared in that shitty medium we
salido en ese medio que es de [__] no
are not going to justify it
lo vamos a justificar
my mother of my mother
madre mía de madre mía
I do not know if people  I would
yo no sé si esto la gente se
consider it lawful but I imagine
consideraría de lícito pero me imagino
that supposedly of course
que por supuestamente que por supuesto
yes and I don't
que sí y no
imagine that of course if not it
me imagino que por supuesto que si no
would be abuse no I believe that you wouldn't
que sería un abuso no yo creo eso no se
[ __ ] a woman who is drunk super
cogerá una mujer que está borracha súper
unconscious overcome colized and drugged
inconsciente superar col izada y drogada
there sleeping naked and take a
ahí durmiendo en pelotas y hacerte una
picture to send it to your friends
foto para mandársela a tus colegas
because I
porque me
[Music]
[Música]
I think that those abuses I'm not
yo creo que esos abusos no lo tengo
sure what the definition would be but I would
claro cuál sería la definición pero yo
say that
diría que
I would say that those abuses
yo diría que esos abusos
god
dios
as she is 34 years old she
como tiene 34 años
doesn't have the mentality of someone of 34
no tiene la mentalidad de alguien de 34
years old going around telling people that
años yendo por ahí diciéndole a la gente
when they come to Spain she is going to
que cuando la venga a españa le va a
blow up as I say to good michu
reventar como le digo a buen michu
maite thank you very much darling for
maite muchísimas gracias corazón por
this super chat
este super chat
[Music]
[Música]